(Sheldon:)How much will it hurt?
(Amy:)It's just
a tiny skin sample.
(Amy:)You saw me
do it to myself.
(Sheldon:)On a scale of one to ten,
where one is a pebble
(Sheldon:)in your shoe
and ten is the monkey
(Sheldon:)you thought was your pet
biting your face off.
(Amy:)A two.
(Sheldon:)Eating a whole Altoid?
(Amy:)Sheldon,
(Amy:)if I'm gonna synthesize
a neural network
(Amy:)from our skin cells,
I need to harvest them.
(Amy:)Now, I've done this dozens
of times, but if you're
(Amy:)too scared
you don't have to.
(Sheldon:)No, this is for science.
(Sheldon:)I can be brave
for science.
(Amy:)Thank you.
Oh, jiminy, that's cold!
(Amy:)Just think how happy
you'll be in a few weeks
(Amy:)when I've converted
our skin cells
(Amy:)into functional
brain cells.
(Sheldon:)All right, just warn me
before you do it.
(Amy:)Okay.
(Amy:)Three...
(Amy:)two...
and we're done.
(Sheldon:)You tricked me.
(Sheldon:)You didn't say one.
(Amy:)It didn't hurt, did it?
No...
but “three, two and we're done”
is incomplete.
(Sheldon:)You know those
things bother me.
(Sheldon:)It's like hearing
“da-da-da-da-da-dah”
(Sheldon:)without yelling...
(Amy:)Okay, fine, one.
(Amy:)Thank you.
Now yell “Charge” and
we can get out of here.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪